Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in what I do.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't wanna live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in wonderland.
It's Crocodile!
He's here to save us!
Crocodile one of the seven
warlords calm down ignorant
peasants i only came to
your pathetic little town
for that pirate's head
he's so great and modest he
comes and saves us but he
won't take the credit for it.
Three cheers for Crocodile!
You peasants can call
me whatever you want.
But you, you pirates should
have stayed out of this country.
Now you're gonna pay.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
I think you're underestimating us a bit.
What are you gonna take us all on?
There are a lot Of us and only one of
you that's right and you're just the
government's little dog who do you think
You are acting like a hero are those
who wish to live lie down now what an
idiot perfect for target Practice get
this guy every last berry
in this town is hard yeah
nothing
but a pathetic puppet
No!
I'm a puppet, huh?
I don't think so, idiot pirate.
We've been saved!
He's leaving now?
Crocodile! Crocodile!
Crocodile! Crocodile! Crocodile!
Crocodile!
Killer -
Looks like he beat us here again.
Seems like he is always one step ahead.
By the time we arrived, the pirates
had already been taken care of. I see.
Well, as long as the citizens are safe,
I suppose there's no need to worry.
Crocodile has been a great help.
There's no mistaking it.
I hope you're ready.
We've almost made it to Alabasta.
Don't lie to me, Luffy.
Tell me what you know right now.
Don't look away from me.
I want you to look me in the eyes
right now and tell me the truth.
No idea what you mean, Saji.
I don't know anything. No clue.
Then let me ask you.
How did enough food for eight people,
which I carefully divided up so that it
would last until we reached Alabasta,
suddenly go missing in
the middle of the night?
Lying is pointless, so
just tell me the truth.
You have a terrible poker face.
Oh, hey, it looks like you have
something around your mouth there.
I forgot about the crumbs.
I knew it was you!
Jerk.
Hey, Nami, we need to do something.
We need a better way of keeping
the food safe from Luffy.
Can we please buy a
refrigerator that locks?
Well, maybe.
Might be a good idea, since it
could be a matter of life and death.
Well, we really do need to
catch something for Sanji.
So, how's the fishing going?
Uh, well, it's a...
I can't take my eyes off anyone.
I'm so hungry!
And the fish aren't biting at all? Really?
You do realize this is your fault?
You ate all the bait that we had.
The fish aren't ever going to bite
if we don't give them a reason!
You ate some too.
But I only ate a little bit
just what was stuck to the lid.
Hey guys, so how's it
going catch anything yet?
Do you think we could catch a shark?
Oh, no, I really want to catch a
sea king Stop fishing with my duck!
You jerk!
Over there, you two.
What is that stuff?
Cotton candy?
You guys wait here.
I'll go get Nami.
Nami, there's something wrong.
Come quickly.
Oh, yeah. I see it.
Nothing to worry about.
It's just a little steam.
You're saying that steam's
coming up out of the ocean?
Uh-huh.
A hot spot, that's all.
What's a hot spot?
An area of the sea where magma's made.
Below the steam over there
is an undersea volcano.
There are volcanoes underneath
the sea? That's right.
In fact, there are actually more volcanoes
under the sea than there are on dry land.
Ooh.
So I guess we can't eat
the steam then, huh?
There will be a brand new island
over there, thanks to the volcano.
But the process will take
tens of thousands of years.
Oh, wow.
You're amazing, Nami.
Wonder if I can live that long.
I'd plan on dying sometime before that.
Have you caught anything?
We're so hungry.
Can't you cook us something?
You guys are just hopeless.
But I'll go search the storage area
anyway to see if we have anything left.
Yuck!
It smells like sulfur!
I can't see anything!
There's steam everywhere!
Disappear with it!
We should be out of the steam soon!
Excuse me, Mr. Two!
What is it now?
There's a whole bunch
of smoke at 12 o 'clock.
I'm not afraid of some smoke.
Keep going.
No matter what, we've
got to take care of Mr.
Three, or else the next
target's going to be me.
Yes, sir.
We're going in.
What is this?
I have no idea. No!
We made it through.
Ah! Mr.
Two has completely disappeared!
Let's check the cabin!
We can't find him! This is
Mr. Two! Where did you know?!
No, really!
This is getting out of hand!
One of these days I need to stop
jumping on every random duck I see!
What is that?
You have to help me, please!
Get me out of here, please!
I can't swim!
I thought I was going to
die there for a minute.
Hey!
You saved me! Thanks!
I never imagined my life would be
saved by a group of complete strangers.
Thanks again.
I'll never forget your kindness.
Although, could I trouble
you for a cup of warm soup?
A chicken noodle will do. No way!
We can't even feed ourselves!
Oh, hey.
You're just an absolute cutie,
aren't you? Oh, yeah. Sexy.
So weird.
So, uh, you really can't swim, huh?
That's right.
You see, I ate a Devil Fruit, so
I can't swim even a little bit.
Yeah?
What kind of fruit?
Let's see.
Well, since I can't go anywhere
until my ship picks me up,
there's no harm in a little fun.
For saving my life, I'll show you.
Now, get ready.
This is my power!
What are you?
Wait, wait.
Hold on a second.
This is all just for a
little fun, remember?
Hey now, mean guy. Relax. Wait.
That's me!
And if I touch my face
with my left hand...
I'm back to normal.
Now that is the power of the
clone clone Devil Fruit, you see.
Amazing.
The body and the voice match perfectly!
There.
But honestly, I didn't really
have to slap you around like that.
Okay?
Now what?
All I have to do is touch
my right hand to you.
As you can see, I can mimic anyone.
That's not all.
I can change bodies, too.
Stop that!
Uh, Guy, are you okay?
Well, I'm terribly sorry, but I
shouldn't demonstrate my power anymore.
No! Please! No more!
Okay.
If you absolutely insist, I
guess I can show a little more.
Oh, man, that's awesome.
He's really hamming it up, huh?
Well, in that case, I have
something even more incredible.
I'm equipped with a memory feature.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Okay.
This is just boring.
And twirl open blue.
Well, did everyone enjoy my
very special secret talent?
It's quite impressive, but
I almost never show it off.
Oh, yeah!
It's too good to be true!
It's too good to be true! Oh, whatever.
Oh, oh!
It's too good to be true!
It's time to say goodbye
already what a shame.
No you can't leave please
don't go try not to
be sad journeys must
always include farewells.
And yet i will never
forget you or today it's
been brief but true friendship
isn't determined? by time.
Don't cry, friends!
See you, Kongo!
Now, quickly, let's be going! Yes,
sir, Mr. Two, Mr. Barclay, sir!
Mr. Two!
That guy is Mr. Two?
Vivi, you mean you didn't
know him just by looking?
Uh-uh, I've never met Mr. Two or Mr.
One and his partner.
I don't know much about any of
them, or what their powers may be.
Though I have heard rumors about them all.
I've heard about Mr. Two.
Apparently, he's a very tall
ballerina who talks like a woman?
and he always wears a swan coat.
The coat says Bon Clay on the back.
I didn't know!
Is something wrong, Vivi?
I saw something in his memory,
in the faces that he showed us.
One of those faces belonged to my father.
Cobra Nefertari, my father,
the king of Alabasta.
That's not good.
If we can mimic the face
of a king that easily, Mr.
Two has the potential to
cause a lot of trouble.
Looks like we let a really
bad guy get away today, huh?
So that guy is our enemy?
Seems so, and having him on the
other side is not a good thing.
If Mr.
Two realizes that we're the
ones Baroque Works is after,
then he can use the memories he got
earlier to transform into any one of us.
We won't even be able to
trust our own friends.
Really?
I'll explain it again.
No, hold on a sec.
Luffy's slow, but he's
right not to be scared.
Just hear me out on this one,
and I think you'll agree.
It's actually a good
thing that we ran into Mr.
Two when we did, because now we can prepare,
and we can beat him at his own game.
You sure seem to be in a particularly
good mood for some reason, Mr.
Two.
Don't you say four again?
It just so happens I made
some new friends today.
The thing is huge!
A sea cat!
That's a sea cat!
It looks like food to me!
Yeah, let's go!
We're on the right track.
Now, if we can just get
there alive, that'd be great.
Food for me!
It's breaking away! Reverse!
Put the boat in reverse! No!
We can't do that!
Hey!
Don't let it get away!
If the two of you don't
capture it, I'll kill you!
Now then, sea kitten, how do
you think I should cook you?
Eevee, what are you doing?
I'm hungry! Why? Just why? It was food!
Because you can't eat a sea cat!
I just can't let you!
Sea cats are sacred animals in Alabasta!
Well, that's good to know.
There are more animals in
the ocean than I thought!
If you're still scared of that stuff,
then you have a long way to go!
So,
let me tell you about
the time that I, Usopp,
single-handedly fought off the sea
kings of the comm belt, young chopper!
Sea kings? Really?
And big ones, too.
Man, they were really huge!
Our food got away!
Yeah, but don't worry, Luffy.
You'll be able to stuff
yourself full really soon.
Yeah, really?
Will we get another cat to eat, Vivi?
Vivi, the wind and weather
seem to be stabilizing. Uh-huh.
We're entering the climate
area of Alabasta Island.
Seeing a seat cat come out of
the water is proof as well.
And those things you
see behind us over there
are all the proof I need
that we're getting close.
It's a lot of ships huh
are they they're all
flying the baroque works
symbol on their mast.
This can't be good it looks as if all the
baroque works employees
have started gathering.
I'm guessing that these
are the billions they're
the subordinates under
the officer agents which
Means that there are at
least 200 enemies waiting
for us the best the
baroque works has to offer.
The elite of the
underlings this group will
surely be a lot better
than the bounty hunters.
At whiskey peak come on
let's blow them all away
it'll be quicker if we
just go over there and
beat Them up hold on though
i need to eat something
first come on they're not
worth it don't bother.
He's right.
We need to keep our eyes on the prize
or we might lose this all together.
After all, eight against
two hundred sucks.
Just make sure and try it tight.
I don't want anyone fooled
by the enemy's disguises.
What a good plan.
We'll always know who our friends are.
Just look for the bandage on their arm.
This clone clone fruit guy.
So, is he that similar when
he turns into someone else?
You have no idea.
It's the same, not just similar.
It was crazy. Really?
You should have seen it, Sanji.
He changed into every
one of us, even Nami.
And then we got to dance with him.
We know that someone with his
powers is among the enemy,
so we need to be really careful
to be on our guard at all times.
So, what should I do to
help against this guy?
Just do whatever it is you can do.
You're not expected to do
anything more, Chopper.
And if you get overwhelmed, then just run.
Sounds like the pep talk
he's always giving himself.
Whatever it is I can do.
I got it.
I can see the island now.
Let's stop at the town called Nanohana.
We have to hide the ship.
Okay, no matter what happens on that island,
remember, this thing on all our arms?
is a sign of our friendship.
Now, let's land, okay?
Then eat.
Oh, and help me to do that.
That's a side note.
Now remember our enemy is
a whole gang of assassins?
Yeah, sure.
Is just try to think before
you do anything stupid.
You got that?
Yeah, of course. You're right.
I got it. Really. I will.